RAPHAEL DO NASCIMENTO BORGES

31 years old, São Bernardo do Campo - SP

Email: raphael.n.borges@gmail.com | + 55 (11) 99017-3638 Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/raphael-do-nascimento-borges/

Github: https://github.com/Rapha-Borges

SUMMARY

ADS student with experience in network infrastructure, cloud providers (AWS, OCI) and containers. Having the Python programming language as the main one.

I work with containers, python and web development (HTML and CSS) in private projects.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Uninter - Systems Analysis and Development - 2nd semester

LANGUAGES

English – Intermediate level French - Basic level

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Staff Burger

Owner - October 2020 - February 2022 Porto Alegre, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil

Picanha Catering

Assistant - July 2018 - August 2019

Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Autonomous

Transport - January 2017 - June 2018

Bettembourg, Luxembourg

Amnesia Bar

General services - October 2015 - January 2017

Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Contax Group

Technical Support - July 2013 - April 2015

Porto Alegre, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil

Companhia Carris Portoalegrense

Support Agent - September 2010 - April 2013 Porto

Alegre, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil

ADDITIONAL COURSES AND EXPERIENCES

AWS Expert - LINUXTips - 34h - 2022

Uncomplicating Docker - LINUXTips - 12h - 2022

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials - Amazon Web Services (AWS) - 6h - 2022

Python for the Web - Alura - 85h - 2022

Impressive Python - Hashtag Training - 100h - 2022

Microsoft S2B Network and Systems Administration - PUC-RS - 2010

SKILLS

- Containers (Kubernetes, Docker)
- Cloud (AWS, OCI)
- Terraform
- Python (Django)
- Web Development (HTML, CSS)
- Network Infrastructure
- Hardware and Operating Systems (Linux, macOS, Windows)
- Version Management Systems (Git, GitHub).